{"__cache./api/resource/task/40396/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40396,"taskName":"Metal Roofing - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Metal Roofing","xmTaskDescriptor":"Metal Roofing Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":2200,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"ARCHITECTURAL ROOFS Roofers License steel","textMessagingName":"Inst Metal Roof","rolloverLongDesc":"Older metal roofs are usually shiny \u0026 sloped with a smooth surface except for vertical ribs spaced every foot or so. Newer metal roofs may be designed to look like slate or tile. This category is for when it is probable that repairs won't be sufficient \u0026 that total replacement is likely to be necessary.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes tin, steel, copper, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Metal Roofing.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Metal Roof Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Metal Roofing","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Metal Roof Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Metal Roofing - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Metal Roofing Project","urlName":"Metal-Roofing-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Metal Roof Installation Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"ARCHITECTURAL,ROOFS,Roofers,License,steel,seam,standing,rooofing,siding,,conctractors,roofers.com,wanted,replacement,designs,bids,,prosource,prescreened,national,local,exterior,corrugated,copper,build,aluminum,Roofs-Metal,exchange,Roofing,METAL","emcCategoryOid":-12061,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":690,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Metal Roofing Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376528849pwspr012F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40396/":{"taskOID":40396,"originalTaskOID":40396,"setID":690,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6869,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5306,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Roof","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of metal roofing do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7206,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Zinc","answerDisplayText":"Zinc","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1634,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Copper","answerDisplayText":"Copper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4772,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Polymer coating","answerDisplayText":"Polymer coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6054,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Standing seam","answerDisplayText":"Standing seam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1652,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Corrugated","answerDisplayText":"Corrugated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5711,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Simulated shake","answerDisplayText":"Simulated shake","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5712,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Simulated shingle","answerDisplayText":"Simulated shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5714,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Simulated tile","answerDisplayText":"Simulated tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5568,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which special features would you like for your roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6871,"questionDisplayText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6869,"questionDisplayText":"What is the nature of this project?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9813,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Completely replace roof","answerDisplayText":"Completely replace roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9814,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Install roof on new construction","answerDisplayText":"Install roof on new construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9815,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing roof","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5306,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Roof","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of metal roofing do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7206,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Zinc","answerDisplayText":"Zinc","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1634,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Copper","answerDisplayText":"Copper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4772,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Polymer coating","answerDisplayText":"Polymer coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6054,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Standing seam","answerDisplayText":"Standing seam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1652,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Corrugated","answerDisplayText":"Corrugated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5711,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Simulated shake","answerDisplayText":"Simulated shake","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5712,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Simulated shingle","answerDisplayText":"Simulated shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5714,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Simulated tile","answerDisplayText":"Simulated tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7206,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Zinc","answerDisplayText":"Zinc","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1634,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Copper","answerDisplayText":"Copper","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4772,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Polymer coating","answerDisplayText":"Polymer coating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6054,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Standing seam","answerDisplayText":"Standing seam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1652,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Corrugated","answerDisplayText":"Corrugated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5711,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Simulated shake","answerDisplayText":"Simulated shake","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5712,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Simulated shingle","answerDisplayText":"Simulated shingle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5714,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Simulated tile","answerDisplayText":"Simulated tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5568,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which special features would you like for your roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5354,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ridge vent","answerDisplayText":"Ridge vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5842,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Snow guards or brackets","answerDisplayText":"Snow guards or brackets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2893,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters and downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Gutters and downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6536,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Turbine vents","answerDisplayText":"Turbine vents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5769,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Skylight/Solar tube","answerDisplayText":"Skylight/Solar tube","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2950,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Heat tape","answerDisplayText":"Heat tape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6857,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Water diverters","answerDisplayText":"Water diverters","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2521,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6872,"questionDisplayText":"Stories in House","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your home?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6871,"questionDisplayText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you aware of any leaks or damage to the roof?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9816,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}